<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.spectacle.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Spectacle</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSpectaclexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Spectacle</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      Spectacle is a simple application for capturing desktop screenshots. It can capture images of the entire desktop, a single monitor, the currently active window, the window currently under the mouse, or a rectangular region of the screen. The images can then be printed, sent to other applications for manipulation, or quickly be saved as-is.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Spectacle és una aplicació per a prendre captures de pantalla de l'escriptori. Pot capturar imatges de tot l'escriptori, un sol monitor, la finestra activa, la finestra sota el ratolí o d'una regió rectangular de la pantalla. Les imatges es poden imprimir, enviar a altres aplicacions per a la seva manipulació o desar-les com estan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'Spectacle és una aplicació per a prendre captures de pantalla de l'escriptori. Pot capturar imatges de tot l'escriptori, un sol monitor, la finestra activa, la finestra sota el ratolí o d'una regió rectangular de la pantalla. Les imatges es poden imprimir, enviar a altres aplicacions per a la seua manipulació o guardar-les com estan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Spectacle is a simple application for capturing desktop screenshots. It can capture images of the entire desktop, a single monitor, the currently active window, the window currently under the mouse, or a rectangular region of the screen. The images can then be printed, sent to other applications for manipulation, or quickly be saved as-is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Spectacle es una sencilla aplicación para realizar capturas de pantalla del escritorio. Puede capturar imágenes de todo el escritorio, de un único monitor, de la ventana activa actual, de la ventana que esté bajo el cursor o de un área rectangular de la pantalla. Las imágenes se pueden imprimir, enviar a otras aplicaciones para su procesamiento o guardar en el disco de forma inmediata.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Spectacle on lihtne ekraanipiltide tegemise rakendus. See võib pildistada tervet töölauda, konkreetset monitori, parajasti aktiivset akent, hiire all olevat akent või ekraanil valitud ristkülikukujulist osa. Tehtud pilte saab trükkida, saata töötlemiseks teistesse rakendustesse või ka lihtsalt kiiresti ja muutmata salvestada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Spectacle on yksinkertainen sovellus ruutukaappauskuvien ottamiseksi. Se voi kaapata kuvan koko työpöydältä, yksittäiseltä näytöltä, aktiivisesta ikkunasta, hiiren alla olevasta ikkunasta tai suorakulmaisesta näytön alueesta. Kuvat voi myöhemmin tulostaa, lähettää muihin sovelluksiin käsiteltäväksi tai tallentaa sellaisinaan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Spectacle è una semplice applicazione per catturare schermate. Può acquisire immagini dell'intero desktop, di un singolo monitor, della finestra attiva, della finestra sotto il puntatore del mouse, o di una regione rettangolare dello schermo. Le immagini possono essere stampate, inviate ad altre applicazioni per essere modificate, o salvate rapidamente così come sono.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Spectacle is een eenvoudige toepassing voor het opnemen van schermafbeeldingen van het bureaublad. Het kan afbeeldingen van het gehele bureaublad, een enkele monitor, het nu actieve venster, het venster nu onder de muis of een rechthoekig gebied van het scherm. De afbeelding kan dan afgedrukt worden, naar een andere toepassing voor bewerking worden verzonden of snel worden opgeslagen zoals deze nu is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Spectacle er eit enkel program for å ta skjermbilete. Det kan ta bilete av heile skrivebordet, ein einskild skjerm, det gjeldande vindauget, vindauget under musepeikaren eller eit utsnitt av skjermflata. Bileta kan skrivast ut, sendast til andre program for vidare arbeid eller lagrast direkte.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Spectacle to prosta aplikacja do wykonywania zrzutów ekranu. Za jej pomocą można przechwycić cały pulpit, pojedynczy monitor, obecnie aktywne okno, okno obecnie pod wskaźnikiem myszy lub prostokątny obszar ekrany. Zrzuty można wydrukować, wysłać do innej aplikacji do obróbki lub szybko zapisać tak jak go wykonano.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Spectacle é uma aplicação simples para capturar imagens do ecrã. Pode capturar imagens de todo o ecrã, de um único monitor, da janela activa no momento, da janela sob o cursor do rato ou de uma região rectangular do ecrã. As imagens poderão então ser impressas, enviadas para outras aplicações para posterior manipulação ou serem gravadas como estão.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Spectacle é um aplicativo simples para tirar capturas de tela da área de trabalho. Ele pode capturar imagens de toda a área de trabalho, de um monitor, da janela ativa, da janela atualmente abaixo do mouse ou de uma região retangular da tela. Estas imagens podem ser impressas, enviadas a outros aplicativos para manipulação ou serem salvas rapidamente como estão.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Spectacle je jednoduchá aplikácia na snímanie plochy. Dokáže zachytiť obrázky celej plochy, jedného monitora, aktívneho okna, okna pod myšou alebo pravouhlej oblasti obrazovky. Obrázky sa dajú tlačiť, poslať do inej aplikácie na manipuláciu alebo rýchlo uložiť tak, ako sú.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Spectacle je preprost program za zajemanje zaslonskih slik namizja. Zajame lahko slike celotnega namizja, enega zaslona, trenutno dejavnega okna, okna pod miško ali pravokotnega območja pod miško. Te slike lahko nato natisnete, pošljete v druge programe ali pa hitro shranite.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Spectacle är ett enkelt program för att ta skärmbilder av skrivbordet. Det kan ta bilder av hela skrivbordet, en enda bildskärm, fönstret som för närvarande är aktivt, fönstret som för närvarande är under musen, eller ett rektangulärt skärmområde. Bilderna kan därefter skrivas ut, skickas till andra program för behandling, eller snabbt sparas som de är.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Spectacle — проста програма для створення знімків екрана. Передбачено можливість захоплення знімків усієї стільниці, окремого монітора, поточного активного вікна, вікна під вказівником миші або прямокутної ділянки на екрані. Створені зображення можна надрукувати, надіслати до іншої програми для обробки або зберегти без змін.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSpectacle is a simple application for capturing desktop screenshots. It can capture images of the entire desktop, a single monitor, the currently active window, the window currently under the mouse, or a rectangular region of the screen. The images can then be printed, sent to other applications for manipulation, or quickly be saved as-is.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Funksjonar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Recursos:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Capture Entire Desktop</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Captura l'escriptori sencer</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Captura l'escriptori sencer</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Zachytit celou plochu</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Die gesamte Arbeitsfläche aufnehmen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Capture Entire Desktop</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Capturar todo el escritorio</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kogu töölaua pildistamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Koko työpöydän kaappaus</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Cattura l'intero desktop</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Opname van het gehele bureaublad</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Ta bilete av heile skrivebordet</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przechwytywanie całego pulpitu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Captura de Todo o Ecrã</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capturar toda a área de trabalho</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zachytiť celú plochu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zajem celotnega namizja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ta en bild av hela skrivbordet</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Захоплення зображення усієї стільниці</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCapture Entire Desktopxx</li>
      <li>Capture Current Monitor</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Captura el monitor actual</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Captura el monitor actual</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Zachytit současný monitor</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Den aktuellen Bildschirm aufnehmen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Capture Current Monitor</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Capturar el monitor actual</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Aktiivse monitori pildistamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Nykyisen näytön kaappaus</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Cattura il monitor attuale</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Opname van de huidige monitor</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Ta bilete av gjeldande skjerm</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przechwytywanie bieżącego monitora</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Captura do Monitor Actual</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capturar o monitor atual</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zachytiť aktuálny monitor</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zajem trenutnega zaslona</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ta en bild av aktuell bildskärm</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Захоплення зображення на поточному моніторі</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCapture Current Monitorxx</li>
      <li>Capture Active Window</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Captura la finestra activa</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Captura la finestra activa</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Zachytit aktivní okno</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Das aktive Fenster aufnehmen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Capture Active Window</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Capturar la ventana activa</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Aktiivse akna pildistamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Aktiivisen ikkunan kaappaus</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Cattura la finestra attiva</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Opname van het actieve venster</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Ta bilete av aktivt vindauge</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przechwytywanie aktywnego okna</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Captura da Janela Activa</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capturar a janela ativa</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zachytiť aktuálne okno</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zajem dejavnega okna</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ta en bild av aktivt fönster</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Захоплення зображення активного вікна</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCapture Active Windowxx</li>
      <li>Capture Rectangular Region</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Captura una regió rectangular</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Captura una regió rectangular</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Zachytit obdélníkovou oblast</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Einen rechteckigen Bereich aufnehmen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Capture Rectangular Region</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Capturar un área rectangular</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ristkülikukujulise ala pildistamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Suorakulmaisen alueen kaappaus</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Cattura una regione rettangolare</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Opname van een rechthoekig gebied</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Ta bilete av skjermutsnitt</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przechwytywanie obszaru prostokątnego</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Captura de uma Região Rectangular</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capturar região retangular</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zachytiť pravouhlú oblasť</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zajem pravokotnega območja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ta en bild av ett rektangulärt område</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Захоплення зображення прямокутної ділянки</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCapture Rectangular Regionxx</li>
      <li>Keyboard shortcuts for taking screenshots</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Dreceres de teclat per a prendre captures de pantalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Dreceres de teclat per a prendre captures de pantalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Kurzbefehle für die Aufnahme von Bildschirmfotos</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Keyboard shortcuts for taking screenshots</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Accesos rápidos de teclado para realizar capturas</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ekraanipildi tegemine kiirklahve kasutades</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Pikanäppäimet kuvakaappausten ottamiseksi</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Scorciatoie di tastiera per acquisire schermate</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Sneltoetsen voor het maken van schermafdrukken</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Snøggtastar for å ta bilete av skjermen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Skróty klawiszowe do wykonywania zrzutów ekranu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Atalhos do teclado para capturar as imagens</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Atalhos de teclado para tirar capturas de tela</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Klávesové skratky na tvorbu snímok</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Tipkovne bližnjice za zajemanje zaslonskih slik</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Snabbtangenter för att ta skärmbilder</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення знімків за допомогою натискання комбінацій клавіш</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxKeyboard shortcuts for taking screenshotsxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="880" height="537">http://kde.org/images/screenshots/spectacle.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://kde.org/applications/graphics/spectacle/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=spectacle</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>spectacle</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
